{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who said: When you're with someone, you put up with the stuff that makes you lose respect for them, and that is love.",
        "answer1": "Jan Levinson",
        "answer2": "Angela Martin",
        "answer3": "Erin Hannon",
        "answer4": "Michael Scott",
        "correctAnswer": "Erin Hannon"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to Dwight Schrute, what is the groin of the head?",
        "answer1": "The mouth",
        "answer2": "The eyes",
        "answer3": "nose",
        "answer4": "ears",
        "correctAnswer": "The eyes"
      },
      {
        "question": "From the episode on Jan's deposition, who was the other 'woman' Michael referred to in his diary as someone just as hot as Jan but in a different way?",
        "answer1": "Carol Stills",
        "answer2": "Karen Filipelli",
        "answer3": "Ryan Howard",
        "answer4": "Holly Flax",
        "correctAnswer": "Ryan Howard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who's ring was taken from the buttocks of his grandmother, put there by the patriarch of the Coors Dynasty, melted in a foundry run by Menonites?",
        "answer1": "Andy Bernard",
        "answer2": "Kevin Malone",
        "answer3": "Creed Bratton",
        "answer4": "Dwight Schrute",
        "correctAnswer": "Dwight Schrute"
      },
      {
        "question": "Complete the last line of Michael's sentence from the Cocktails episode at David Wallace's home:  Rachel thinks that I brought homemade potato salad. But I just picked it up at the supermarket. It's funny. I wish I could make potato salad that good. It's just potatoes and mayonnaise.",
        "answer1": "On an unrelated note if you feel sick.. maybe don't eat the mayonnaise",
        "answer2": "...The sun has been beating down on the mayonnaise",
        "answer3": "Jan didn't want to come to the cocktail party",
        "answer4": "There's something wrong with Jan",
        "correctAnswer": "There's something wrong with Jan"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of that weird song Jan liked so much from her assistant, Hunter?",
        "answer1": "That One Night",
        "answer2": "You Made Everything Alright",
        "answer3": "Made Me A Man",
        "answer4": "You Took Me By The Hand",
        "correctAnswer": "That One Night"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who kissed Andy Bernard right before leaving the company?",
        "answer1": "Robert California",
        "answer2": "Erin Hannon",
        "answer3": "Kelly Kapoor",
        "answer4": "Oscar Martinez",
        "correctAnswer": "Robert California"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why does Michael do a Yoda voice impersonation during his proposal to Holly Flax?",
        "answer1": "They both love Yoda",
        "answer2": "Yoda voice impersonation was their first love connection",
        "answer3": "Michael gets weird and awkward when he's nervous",
        "answer4": "They had been doing voice impersonations all day",
        "correctAnswer": "Yoda voice impersonation was their first love connection"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which character sleeps at the office 4 nights a week?",
        "answer1": "Meredith Palmer",
        "answer2": "Creed Bratton",
        "answer3": "Darryl Philbin",
        "answer4": "Dwight Schrute",
        "correctAnswer": "Creed Bratton"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why does Pam refuse to go to sports games with Roy?",
        "answer1": "She doesn't like sports or Roy's brother",
        "answer2": "Somebody threw their drink on her last time she went to a game with him and his brother",
        "answer3": "Roy and his brother got very rowdy and competitive at the last College Football game they attended",
        "answer4": "Roy left her at a minor league hockey game by accident on their first date",
        "correctAnswer": "Roy left her at a minor league hockey game by accident on their first date"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which character said: There's too many people on this earth.. We need a new plague",
        "answer1": "Stanley Hudson",
        "answer2": "Dwight Schrute",
        "answer3": "Hank the security guard",
        "answer4": "Angela Martin",
        "correctAnswer": "Dwight Schrute"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where was Jim and Pam's first kiss?",
        "answer1": "Chilli's at the Dundie Awards Ceremony",
        "answer2": "Casino Night in the Warehouse",
        "answer3": "The break room",
        "answer4": "In the parking lot",
        "correctAnswer": "Chilli's at the Dundie Awards Ceremony"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which character said: Make friends first, make sales second & make love third.  In no particular order.",
        "answer1": "Meredith Palmer",
        "answer2": "Creed Bratton",
        "answer3": "Michael Scott",
        "answer4": "Todd Packer",
        "correctAnswer": "Michael Scott"
      }
    ]
  }